Guide to the Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Collection 1938-[1970-1998] 2000
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Series VI: Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Central Records Library
  - Sub-series 1: Central Records Library
    The bulk of the CRL contains the staggering amount of communication the Trust conducted with the 218,000 claimants and with the attorneys who represented about 28% of them. One copy has been retained of each form or letter preserved in the CRL. In addition to mailings to claimants, the files document such matters as staff training; scripts for verbal communication with claimants; procedures for handling the various options; procedures for settlement conferences, ADR, and arbitration; the special program for assisting claimants seeking in vitro fertilization; pro rata payments; the financial management of the Trust; and Trust termination.
    Please note that the CRL does not contain information about individual claims, claimants, or awards.
    - CRL 0001 Initial Notice to File a Claim with the U.S. Bankruptcy Court 1985 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0002 Pleading by A.H. Robins Relating to the Breland Class Action 1989 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0003 Summary of A.H. Robins Product Litigation System (PLS) (ARC471) 1988 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0004 Objection of A.H. Robins to Bankruptcy Rules 3003 and 3007 to Certain Untimely DS Claims 1988 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0005 List of Robins Documents 1989 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0006 List of Participants in the A.H. Robins Removal Program 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0007 List of A.H. Robins Pending Lawsuits (ARC43) 1989 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0008 A.H. Robins Report on Plan of Reorganization 1988 (Box 1)
    - CRL 0009 A.H. Robins Bar Date Master Pleadings 1985-1988, 12 folders (Box 1-4)
    - CRL 0010 Records and Briefs Filed in the Fourth Circuit Before and During Bankruptcy Proceedings 1985-1989, 10 folders (Box 4-7)
      Arranged by docket number
    - CRL 0011 Disallowance Tape from A.H. Robins 1988 (Box 7)
    - CRL 0012 A.H. Robins Packets 1990 (Oversize Box 143)
    - CRL 0013 Agreement for Transfer of Funds from Robins to Trust 1990 (Box 7)
    - CRL 0014 A.H. Robins' Report of Pre-bankruptcy Legal Cost Management 1984, 1994 (Box 7)
    - CRL 0015 Copies of Partial Testimonies by Dr. Davis Re: Initial Insertion Dates for DS Users 1988 (Box 7)
    - CRL 0100 Scrapbooks Containing Articles Regarding the DS, Bankruptcy Case, Trust, Claims Deadlines, etc. 1974-1991, 6 folders (Box 7, 7a, 8)
    - CRL 1001 Notice of Special Program for Reconstructive Surgery and IVF (ARC264) [1987] (Box 8)
    - CRL 1002 Notice Regarding Reinstatement of Claim 1987 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1003 Questionnaire and Claim Form #1 (ARC268) 1987 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1004 Notice and Questionnaire #2 1987 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1005 Schedule of Liabilities 1989 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1006 Motion for Emergency Relief by the Dalkon Shield Claimants Committee 1988 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1007 Notice of Hearing on Motion For Administrative Order (ARC114) 1991 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1007a Transcript of Hearing for Motion Re: Administrative Order 1991 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1008 SRA Records Status Report 18-Mar-88 1988 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1009 Memorandum Re: Late Claim Pleadings, Deceased Claimants 1988 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1010 Summary of 100 Explanation Forms from Claimants Whose Claims had been Disallowed and were Requesting Reinstatement 1987 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1011 Notice of Disallowance Due to No Submission of Q1 or Q2; Deadline for Filing Objection Included 1987 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1012 Memorandum Regarding Appeals From Orders Denying Reinstatement to DSCT 1988 (Box 8)
    - CRL 1014 Claims Resolution Facility Plan 1987 (Box 8)
    - [CRL 1015] Pre-Consummation Proceedings [Trustee Removal] 1988-1989, 10 folders (Box 9-10)
    - CRL 1016 Original User Claim Packet Sent by Court for Estimation Purposes 1986 (Box 11)
    - CRL 1017 Original Adult Non User Claim Packet Sent Out by the Courts for the Estimation Process 1986 (Box 11)
    - CRL 1018 Original Child Claim Packet Sent by the Court to be Used in the Estimation Process 1986 (Box 11)
    - CRL 1019 Notice of Hearing on Confirmation of Debtors Plan of Reorganization 1988 (Box 11)
    - CRL 1020 Cadwalader Pleadings 1988 (Box 11)
    - CRL 1021 Gallaway Pleadings 1987-1992, 5 folders (Box 11-12)
    - CRL 1022 Rogers Pleadings 1990-1991, 3 folders (Box 12)
    - CRL 1023 Confirmation Pleadings 1988, 1991 (Box 12)
    - CRL 1024 Breland Pleadings 1988-1989 (Box 13)
    - CRL 1025 Estimation Pleadings 1988, 1991 (Box 13)
    - CRL 1026 Williams Pleadings 1982-1994, 4 folders (Box 13-14)
    - CRL 1027 Dill Pleadings 1990-1991, 6 folders (Box 14-15)
    - CRL 1028 Declaration of John D. Taylor Re: Compliance with Order for Bar Date Notification Program 1986 (Box 15)
    - CRL 1029 Various Form Letters Used by the Bankruptcy Court for Claims n.d. (Box 15)
    - CRL 2000 McGovern Study. Questionnaire and Forms Sent to Random Sample of Claimants 1986-1988 (Box 15)
    - CRL 2001 McGovern Study Participant Listing 1990-1991 (Box 15)
    - CRL 2003, 2006 Survey Research Associates [SRA], Training Notes and Manual and List of SRA System Codes and Forms 1986-1987 (Box 15)
    - CRL 2004 SRA Review Log n.d. (Box 16)
    - CRL 2005 List of SRA File Integrations n.d. (Box 16)
    - CRL 2007 Notice to Non-Users of the DS; SRA Court Correspondence to Claimants 1986 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2008 SRA File Audit Priority Status Guidelines 1986-1987 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2009 [McGovern] Priority Claims List 1990 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2010 SRA/McGovern Audit 1990 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2012 List of SRA Claimants n.d., 1990 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2013 Samples and Programs for Analyzing McGovern Study Results 1989 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2014 Computer File Descriptions for PLS System, Law-Firm Look Up Tables, and Frozen Claims 1989 (Box 16)
    - CRL 2017 SRA Documents 1986-1995, 3 folders (Box 17)
    - CRL 3001 Information on Option 1 Election 1988 (Box 17)
    - CRL 3002 Status Report on Trust 20-Apr-89 1989 (Box 17)
    - CRL 3003 Primary Excess Policy From Aetna (ARC58) 1989 (Box 17)
    - CRL 3004 Notice of Hearing on Adequacy of Disclosure Statement (ARC254) 1987 (Box 17)
    - CRL 4001 Consummation of 6th Amended and Restate Plan of Reorganization (The Plan), 3 bound volumes
    - CRL 4002 Ordered Entered 22-May-95 Upholding the Order Limiting Attorney Fees to 10% of the Pro Rata Distribution 1995, 4 folders (Box 18)
    - CRL 4003 Order Dated 10/20/95 Regarding Payment of Pro Rata Distribution Funds 1995 (Box 18)
    - CRL 4004 Order Disallowing Unreasonable Attorney Fees on Pro Rata Distribution 1995 (Box 18)
    - CRL 4005 Notice of Entry of Administrative Order Number 1 Governing DSCT Arbitration and Litigation 1991, 1995 (Box 19)
    - CRL 4006 Protective Order 1992 (Box 19)
    - CRL 4007 Order Approving Insurance Trust Agreement for the Breland Class Action 1988 (Box 19)
    - CRL 4009 Order Setting Time Within Which Certified Claimants Must Commence or Recommence Litigation Against the DSCT 1995, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - CRL 4010 Order Disallowing Twelve OTR Claims 1991 (Box 19)
    - CRL 4011 Collection of Court Rulings, Orders, Opinions, etc 1990-1997, 6 folders (Box 19-20)
    - CRL 4012 Order Vacating 11/13/85 Order, Fixes Bar Date as of 4/30/86, and Approves Form of Notice of Bar Date, Entered 11/22/85 by Judge Merhige 1985 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4014 Order Upholding Pro Rata Fees Limit 1996 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4015 Order Establishing Emergency Fund for Special Program, Entered 5/21/87 1987 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4016 Order Regarding Disposition of Pre-petition Case Files 1998 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4017 Motions by the DSCT to Close OTR into DSCT 1996 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4018 Transcripts and Exhibits for Pro Rata Fees Limitation Hearing 1995 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4019 Order Approving Notice to Termination of Breland Insurance Trust 1998 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4020 Order Regarding the Payment of Unpaid Arbitration Fees 1998 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4021 Work Papers for Appeals to the Order Limiting Fees from Pro Rata Payments 1995 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4022 Order Regarding the Termination of OTR and Transfer of Funds 1996 (Box 20)
    - CRL 4023 Order Terminating the Breland Insurance Trust 1998 (Box 20)
    - CRL 5001-5004 Photocopy Request (ARC166); Acknowledgement of Additional Information; Form Letter Listing Multiple Responses to Generic Question; Notice of Merger of Duplicate Claims n.d. (Box 20)
    - CRL 5005 Various Versions (Undated) of the Address Update Letter, Revised as Postcard 12/18/95 n.d. (Box 20)
    - CRL 5006-5011 Claimant Withdraw Form; Address Update Letter; Attorney Letter Asking them to Forward the Newsletters; Postcard Acknowledging Receipt of Claim Packet; Request for Re-Review Acknowledgement Letters n.d. (Box 20)
    - CRL 5012-5047 Form Letters Used by Breland Insurance Trust n.d. (Box 20)
    - CRL 5048-5049 Identify Your Claim Letter #2; Option 2 Follow-Up Letter OPT2_FUP 1990, 1993 (Box 20)
    - CRL 5050 Postcard Acknowledging the Receipt of the Rejection/ADR Election [1995] (Box 21)
    - CRL 5051 SC Requests for Conference Location Letters n.d. (Box 21)
    - CRL 5052 Letter Responding to Inquiries Re Additional Pro Rata Payments n.d. (Box 21)
    - CRL 6000 PBC Forms for Claims Department Performance Evaluation [1992-1993] (Box 21)
    - CRL 6001 Claims Dept. Various Forms [1991] (Box 21)
    - CRL 6002 Option 2 and B Evaluation Forms and Policies and Procedures n.d. (Box 21)
    - CRL 6003-6037 Miscellaneous Forms n.d. (Box 21)
    - CRL 6038 Reclassification Letters and Forms 1977-1998 (Box 21)
    - CRL 6040 Request for Replacement Pro Rata Check Form 1996 (Box 21)
    - CRL 6041 Summary of Letters Included in the Blank Forms Directory as of 5/20/96 1996 (Box 21)
    - CRL 7001 Memos Regarding Future Plans for Downsizing 1993 (Box 21)
    - CRL 7002 Attorney Merge Project 1990 (Box 21)
      File removed by DSCT, 2/2004
    - CRL 7004 Job Descriptions 1992, 1994 (Box 21)
    - CRL 7005 Employee Survey 1992 (Box 21)
    - CRL 7006 Memorandum Regarding Datastor Boxes 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - CRL 7008 System Design Specifications for Option 1 Mailing 1988 (Box 22)
    - CRL 7010 Summary of Reassignment of Unused LDS Numbers 1989 (Box 22)
    - CRL 7011 DSCT Structure Charts 1995-1997 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8000A Breland and OTR Contracts and Agreements 1991-1996, 2 folders (Box 22)
    - CRL 8001 Furniture Sale Between A.H. Robins and DSCT 1988 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8002 Directors and Officers Liability Policy 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8003 1st and 2nd Outlier Policy 1989, 1992 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8004 Management Agreement Between DSCT and Breland Insurance Trust 1995 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8005 Management Agreement Between DSCT and OTR 1992, 1994 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8006 Lease Between 500 Cary Street Corp. as Landlord and DSCT as Tenant 1993 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8007 Lease for Exchange Place Building 1987-1991 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8008-8009 Database Service Agreement; Proposal to Use Database for Storage of Microfilm n.d. (Box 22)
    - CRL 8012 Radio Station License 1991 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8013 Service Agreement with Equifax for Dtech Services 1990 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8014 Scudder Agreement for Trustee Services 1991 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8015 Lease of the Breland Matter Correspondence System by Aetna 1990-1991 (Box 22)
    - CRL 8016 Assignments of Insurance Claims and Policies for Consummation 1989 (Box 22a)
    - CRL 8017 OTR Agreement Pursuant to the 6th Amended and Restated Plan 1989 (Box 22a)
    - CRL 8018 Escrow Agreements 1989 (Box 22a)
    - CRL 8019-8019A Custody, Claims Processing and Securities Lending Agreement; Custodial Agreement Dated 8/22/88 1988-1989 (Box 22a)
    - CRL 8020 Tax Characterization Agreement 1990 (Box 22a)
    - CRL 8021 Blue Cross/Blue Shield Select Plan Contracts for Health Insurance n.d. (Box 23)
    - CRL 8022 Integrated Flexible Benefits Plan for Employers 1989 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8023 UNUM Employee Benefits 1988 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8024 [DSCT Employee's 401K Plan]. Summary Plan Description 1989-1991 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8025 BC/BS Policies for Health Insurance 1989-1994 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8026 Memorandum Regarding Aetna Insurance 1989 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8028-8029 Agreement Between Scudder Trust Company and DSCT; [Scudder] 401K Program Prototype Plan 1991 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8031 Crestar Custody and Investment Agreements 1989, 1993-1994, 1996 (Box 23)
    - CRL 8032 Background Documents on the Transition from Crestar to First Union 1997 (Box 23)
    - Trustee Removal-Bankruptcy Court Pleadings; 4th Circuit Records and Briefs; Lawyers' Fees 1998-1989 (Box 23)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Minutes 1988, 5 folders (Box 23a)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting: 2/18/1992; 1992, Feb., 3 folders (Box 23b)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 4/9/1992; 1992, Apr. (Box 23b)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 6/26/1992; 1992, Jun., 4 folders (Box 23c)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 9/3-9/1992; 1992, Sep., 2 folders (Box 23c)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 12/15/1992; 1992, Dec. (Box 23d)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 2/17-18/1993; 1993, Feb., 3 folders (Box 23d)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 6/14/1993; 1993, Jun. (Box 23d)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 8/3/1993; 1993, Aug. (Box 23d)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 9/1/1993; 1993, Sep. (Box 23e)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 11/5/1993; 1993, Nov. (Box 23e)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 1/27/1994; 1994, Jan. (Box 23e)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 5/18/1994; 1994, May (Box 23f)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 7/28/1994; 1994, Jul. (Box 23f)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 9/8/1994; 1994, Sep. (Box 23f)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 11/13-14/1994; 1994, Nov. (Box 23f)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 1/30/1995; 1995, Jan. (Box 23g)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 2/27/1995; 1995, Feb., 2 folders (Box 23g)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 4/25/1995; 1995, Apr. (Box 23g)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 6/22/1995; 1995, Jun. (Box 23g)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 9/29/1995; 1995, Sep. (Box 23h)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 11/3/1995; 1995, Nov. (Box 23h)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 1/11/1996; 1996, Jan. (Box 23h)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 4/25-26/1996; 1996, Apr., 3 folders (Box 23h)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 6/25/1996. 1996, Jun. (Box 23i)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 10/2/1996; 1996, Oct., 3 folders (Box 23i)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Crestar/Capitoline Dispute 1996, Oct. (Box 23i)
    - Litigation and Arbitration Report Prepared for Trustees 1996, Dec. (Box 23i)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 12/18/1996; 1996, Dec. (Box 23j)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Conference Call 1/15/1997; 1997, Jan. (Box 23j)
    - Legal Report 1997, Feb. (Box 23j)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 2/17/1997; 1997, Feb., 2 folders (Box 23j)
    - Closedown Committee Meeting 4/17/1997; 1997, Apr. (Box 23j)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 4/28/1997; 1997, Apr. (Box 23j)
    - CRL 9001 DSCT Board of Trustees Meeting 6/24/1997; 1997, Jun. (Box 23j)
    - CRL 9002 Overview of Trust Operations and Summary of Future Plans 1992-1994, 1996 (Box 24)
    - CRL 9003 Proposal for Directors and Officers Liability n.d. (Box 25)
    - CRL 9004 Summary of Estimation of Fund Requirements for the DSCT 1987 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9005, 9021 DSCT By-laws and Interim By-laws 1988 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9006 "The DSCT: Paradigm Lost (or Found)?"; Article Written by Georgene Vairo in Fordham Law Review 1992 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9007 Summary of Travel Expenses 1993 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9008 Summary of Presentation to Trustees of Management Projects (1991); 1991 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9009 Report of Current and Future Liabilities for the Breland Trust 1993 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9010 Report of Plan to Restructure Plan of the Trust [and Planning Team Recommendations] 1993-1994 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9011 Proposals from Various Sources for the NTP Services in Arbitration 1991, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - CRL 9012 Letter Certifying that John Dowd has Returned All Information Pertaining to the Trust and Has Kept No Copies 1992 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9013 Reports of Structured Settlement Proposals and Requirements 1991 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9014 Transcription of Orlando ATLA Meeting 1990 (Box 25)
    - CRL 9019 Option 2/3 Status and Expert Proposals 1989 (Box 25a)
    - CRL 9016 Performance Report of Investments 1990 (Box 26)
    - CRL 9017 Public Information Release; Nomination of Georgene Vairo as a Trustee 1988 (Box 26)
      File Removed by DSCT Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 9020 Budget Recommendations 1996 (Box 26)
    - CRL 9022 Trustee Notification of Discounted Dividend 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 9023 Resolution Allowing Reductions from the Other Claimants Trust Reserve Account 1998 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10000 Letter Dated 7/7/95 Warning FDR [Final Dispute Resolution] Claimants of 9/1/95 Deadline Mailing 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10001-10003 Letters Informing Claimants of Deadlines 1989, 1992, 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10004 Letter to Irish Dalkon Shield Association 1989 (Box 26)
    - CRl 10005 Letter Warning of 7/1/92 for Breland Claimants to Submit Claim Forms 1992 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10006-10007 Notice of Possible Disallowance: Postcard Warning of Deadline to Elect an Option 1991 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10009 Postcard Warning of Breland Deadline to Elect Option 3 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10010-10011 Letter Warning to Claimants of the 7/14/95 Deadline to Submit Option 3 Packets and Deadline to Accept Their Offers; Letter Warning of Deadline to Elect Option 3 and to Submit Releases 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10012-10014 Letter Warning of Breland Deadline to File an Option C and Deadline to Accept or Reject/Elect Offer; Postcard from Breland Acknowledging Receipt of Intent to Participate 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10016-10017 Letter Warning of the 9/1/95 Deadline; Letter Warning Certified Claimants of the 9/1/95 Deadline 1995 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10018 Letter Warning of LDS Deadline (#1) of the 6/30/95 Deadline 1995, 2 folders (Box 26)
    - CRL 10019 Letter Warning Claimants with Uncashed Settlement Checks of the 9/1/94 Deadline to Cash Their Checks 1994 (Box 26)
    - CRL 10020 Letter Warning of the 8/1/94 Deadline to Submit Completed Claim Material 1994 (Box 27)
      Mailing list removed by DSCT Redaction Team, 2/2004
    - CRL 10021 Postcard Warning of the 8/1/94 Deadline to Submit Claim Material 1994 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10022-10024 Postcards Warning of the 9/1/95 Deadline 1995 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10025 LDS Notice of 6/30/94 Deadline for Filing Materials 1994 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10026 Generic Postcard Sent to Claimants to Elect ADR/SC n.d. (Box 27)
    - CRL 10027 Breland Warning of 12/31/95 Deadline to Accept Offer 1995 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10028 Letter to Opt B Claimants Stating that they Must Accept their Offer by 12/31/95 Deadline 1995 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10029-10033 Letters and Postcard Notifying Claimants of Deadlines 1995-1996 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10034 Press Release Dated 4/29/96 Re: ADR Deadline, 25% Pro Rata Payment and ADR Stats 1996 (Box 27)
    - CRL 10035 Listing of Claims Disallowed as a Result of 5/1/96 Deadline 1996 (Box 27)
    - CRL 11001 External Financial Statements for DSCT 1988-1998 (Box 27-29)
    - CRL 11002 External Financial Reports for Breland Insurance Trust 1991-1998 (Box 29)
    - CRL 11003 External Financial Statements for OTR 1989-1991 (Box 30)
    - CRL 11004 Financial Statements for DSCT 1990-1996 (Box 30-46)
    - CRL 11005 Financial Statements for Breland Insurance Trust 1990-1996, 1 binder per month, '93-'95 (Box 46-51)
    - CRL 11006 Financial Reports for OTR [Other Claimants Trust] 1990-1994, Dec. 1995 (Box 52-54)
    - CRL 11007 IRS Letter Approving the Plan 1991 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11009 Crestar 401K Plan and Statement 1989-1990, 3 folders (Box 55)
    - CRL 11010 Breland Insurance Tax Form 1041 with Supplements 1990 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11011 5500 Tax forms for DSCT 1989-1990, 1993-1994 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11012 Form 5032 to IRS 1991 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11013 Financial Investment Surveys for OTR 1991 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11014-11018 DSCT Group Insurance Policies n.d. (Box 55)
    - CRL 11019 Employer Information Report 1990-1991 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11020 5500 Tax Report of Employee Benefits 1994-1997 (Box 55)
    - CRL 11021 Taxibility Issues (Memos) 1988-1997 (Box 55)
    - CRL 12001-12009 Option 1 Forms, Letters, Q and A Sheets and Informations Sheets 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 56)
    - CRL 12100-12120 Option 2 Booklets, Information Sheets, Payment Schedule, Instruction Sheet, Affidavit Form, Medical Records Request Form, Authorization Form; Option 2 Child Election Packet n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12200-12216 Option 3 User Claim Books, Information Letter, Instruction to Retrieve Medical Records, Affidavit Form, Medical Request Form, Authorization Form, Wrongful Death Packet n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12300-12304 Option 4 User Claims Forms, Information Sheet n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12400 Option 5 Voluntary Withdrawal of Claim Form n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12600 User Election Packet n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12601 Non-User Election Packet n.d. (Box 56)
    - CRL 12602 Child Election Packet n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12700-12701 Breland User and Non-User Option A Claim Forms [1996] (Box 57)
    - CRL 12750-12751 Breland User and Non-User Option B Forms n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12800-12802 Breland User, Non-User, and Child Option C Claim Forms [1995] (Box 57)
    - CRL 12850-12851 Breland User and Non-User Option D Claim Form n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12900-12901 Quick Payment Questionnaire and General Release of Claim (Option Q Claim Form); Voluntary Withdrawal Form n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12950-12960 Breland Insurance Trust Letters, Questionnaires, Instructions, Forms, Option Sheets, etc. n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12970-12971 Breland User and Non-User Claim Packets n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 12972-12973 Breland Rejection and Election Form; Notification of 12/31/95 Deadline for Bit Option B Claimants 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 12999 Late Claim Form n.d. (Box 57)
    - CRL 13000 Pro Rata Check Stuffer 1995-1996 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13001 Breland Reinstatement Requests 1992 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13002 Bit Claim with LDS Claim Status Letter 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13003-13004 Letters Informing Claimants of 60% Distribution; Letter to Joint Claimants Eligible for Pro Rata 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13005 Letter Requesting the Claimant to Indicate if the Claimant was a User, Husband, Child, Father, or Other 1990 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13006 Dear Doctor Letter 1990 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13008 Category 5 Letter Warning of the 9/1/94 Deadline to Accept or Reject/Elect 1994 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13009 Letter Warning of the Withdrawal of the Offer at the 91st Day 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13010 Letter to LDS Appellants of the Request to Make Timely to Court 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13011 Mailing to Attorneys of Late Claim Appeals 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13012 No-elects Deadline to Elect 5/8/95 1995 (Box 57)
    - CRL 13013 Order Disallowing Unreasonable Attorneys Fees on Pro Rata Distribution 1995, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - CRL 13014 Notice of Deadline to Reactivate the Option 4 and File a Claim 1995 (Box 58)
    - CRL 13015 Claims Resolution Election Form for ADR/LIT/ARB 1995 (Box 58)
    - CRL 13016 Breland Distribution Letter 1995 (Box 58)
    - CRL 13017 Late Claim Made Timely Letter (Option 3 Claims) 1995, 2 folders (Box 58)
    - CRL 13018 Letter Reporting Order to Make Late Claims Timely, Mailing List Provided 1995 (Box 58)
    - CRL 13019 Re-review Request Form Mailing 1994 (Box 58)